http://www.garlicgourmay.com/pages/garlic-gourmay-privacy-policy

Garlic Gourmay Privacy Policy
The Garlic Gourmay takes your privacy seriously. It is our policy to allow our garlicgourmay.com ("website") customers to provide as much — or as little — personal information to us as they feel comfortable providing. If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy, please contact us and we'll be happy to address your concerns.
Types of Information We Collect
You do not have to provide any personal information to us in order to use our website. The only personal information that we collect from you is information that you choose to submit to us through orders, feedback or information that you otherwise send to us via e-mail ("Personal Information"). Your Personal Information may include your name, address, e-mail address. We may also collect anonymous and aggregate information about your use of our website, such as page hits, numbers of visits, web pages viewed and the length of visits to our website. We do not tie this information to your Personal Information.
Garlic Gourmay Protection Methodology
The Garlic Goumay’s Website operates on a secure server protected by industry standard firewall and password protected systems, and maintains physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to guard the integrity and privacy of these servers and of your Personal Information. Personal Information is processed on a secure server and is transmitted with industry standard technology.
Children's Guidelines
Garlic Gourmay is concerned about the safety and privacy of all its users, particularly children. For this reason, Garlic Gourmay will not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 18. By using our website, you represent to us that you are at least 18 years old. If you are under 18, please do not submit any personal information to us.
How Garlic Gourmay Uses Information Collected
Generally, personal information that you provide through our website is collected and maintained by Garlic Gourmay to enhance our customers' experiences on our website and for correspondence purposes. We may also use your personal information, alone or in combination with the information submitted by other users, to improve our website's navigation or infrastructure; to market and advertise our products or services; to facilitate systems administration and troubleshooting; and for other purposes. We will use the aggregate and anonymous website usage statistics relating to all users to enhance our website's functionality and performance.
Protecting Our Community
To protect our user community, we may use and disclose any information about you to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties, as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate to address or resolve inquiries or problems. We may also disclose such information to third parties as we believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with any merger or consolidation with, or sale of substantially all of our assets to, a third party, provided that such third party agrees to comply with the privacy policy that applies to your Personal Information and that appropriate notices are provided to you.
Use of Our Site is Your Choice
The products and services that we offer on Garlic Gourmay website are entirely voluntary. It is your choice to "opt-in" to participate in any of the services provided therein.
Changing Your Information
If you have moved and/or changed email address, or otherwise need to update or verify your personal information, please contact us at Garlic Gourmay, PO Box 425 Ariel, WA 98603. Upon your request, Garlic Gourmay will remove your personal information from our active database as soon as reasonably possible, unless we need to retain information for dispute resolution, troubleshooting and other valid legal or business reasons. Please note that we will not remove your historical usage information.
Policy Modifications
Garlic Gourmay may change this privacy policy from time to time. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically.
Sign Up for our Newsletter
Subscribe to our newsletter and always be the first to hear about what is happening.
© 2020 Garlic Gourmay.
